<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Compiler Design</title><link>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Compiler Design</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>General information</title><link>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/syllabus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 23:30:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/syllabus/</guid><description>Overview This course is intended to explore the principal ideas and techniques of compiler construction. Topics include lexical analysis, syntax analysis including LL and LR parsers, type checking, run-time environments, symbol tables, code generation, and compiler-construction tools.
This course aims to give you a solid foundation in the theory of compiler construction as well as the experience of building a compiler. Much of what you have learned about algorithms and data structures will come to bear as you study and implement the various components of a compiler.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/schedule/</guid><description>Week by week schedule Week Lecture Note Readings Projects 1 Course Introduction &amp;amp; Overview Lec0 Ch1 2 Regular and Context-Free Languages Lec1 Ch3 3 Lexical Analysis / Lex - The Lexical-Analyzer Generator Lec2 Lec3 Lec4 Ch3 P1 out 4 Top-Down Parsing Lec5 Lec6 Ch4 5 Buttom-Up Parsing/SpringBreak Lec7 Ch4 P1 due 6 Buttom-Up Parsing Ch4 P2 out 7 Yacc - The Parser Generator / Syntax-Directed Translation Lec8 Lec9 Ch5 P2 out 8 Syntax-Directed Translation Ch5 P2 due 9 Midterm Exam P3 out 10 Syntax-Directed Translation / Intermediate-Code Generation Lec10 Ch 5/6 11 Intermediate-Code Generation Ch 6 12 Intermediate-Code Generation Ch 6 P3 due</description></item><item><title/><link>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://compiler-inservice-s22.github.io/docs/guide/</guid><description>Lecture navigation Introduction Organization navigation How to join the organization Introduction Hello! Welcome to the compiler course by Professor Yi-Ping You.
This course has been highly integrated with Github and aimed to improve the students' course-taking experience and try to keep up with the technology trends. In addition, the descriptions and requirements of the homework assignments have also been revised. We hope everyone has a great semester of learning.</description></item></channel></rss>